thank you Steve and good evening
everybody and thank you for joining the
earnings conference call of ICICI
Lombard for q4 FY 2020 and for the full
year of 2020 so I would like to give you
a brief overview of the recent
developments in the industry and our
responses to them or switch our CFO mr.
Gopal Balachandran will share the
financial performance of the country now
as we speak today we are operating in
unprecedented times the Cova 19 pandemic
has disrupted every aspect of our life
at the last count the virus has affected
the 210 countries across the globe as
far as english concerned timely measures
taken by the states such as we
countrywide lockdown to break the
transmission chain calibration of trade
and commercial commerce activity social
distancing normal cetera have helped
limit the contagion at the same time
this would lead to significant economic
impact the extent of which is not
exactly quantifiable at this stage not
Isis is numbered we have reorganized
ourselves to service our customers and
support our channel partners while
ensuring the safety and well-being of
our employees we've been able to achieve
thanks to the technology that we have
travels over over a decade to really
customize can experience the entire
insurance process from purchase to
policy servicing to claim intimation to
renewal in the digital mode right at the
purchase stage we offer multiple options
for
transacting through web mobile apps
cetera today about 96.5% of policies
issued by us our in paperless form with
regard to clean settlement we offer
multiple digital solutions for quick
processing a case to the point is
introspect for motor owned damage claims
the feature available on our mobile app
does away with the need to physically
survey that ever damaged vehicle
allowing real-time claim assessment in
approval since its inspection inception
in the 2017 we have approved more than
six and a half lakh claims instantly
throughout using in suspect during the
lockdown we managed to conduct damage
assessment of 100 percent of the cases
using in suspect on the health insurance
front we introduced an AI enable
settlement engine to authorize some of
the health claims during the lockdown in
April 31 personal all the health claims
were authorized using this tool for
policy servicing and query resolution we
are encouraging our customers to make
use of our digital solutions I must make
the lockdown we have experienced that
more than 50% of the customers calling
the call center prefer to opt for
advocate phones when given the option to
do so we are heartened by this response
to the same as we look ahead we will
continue to promote our digital services
available 24 by 7 to our customers now
going beyond customer support we've been
pursuing ways to truly address customer
needs in these challenging times we
introduce a dedicated product oven 19 a
production cover that provides 100% of
some ensured on the first diagnosis of
the virus we have offered this relevant
proposition across channels including
entering two types with entity such as
flip card bars etcetera to reach their
customer base now missus log lockdown
obtaining medical advice is a big
challenge
so harnessing our health ecosystem and
the technological prowess we've
introduced a telecon search feature on
our mobile app I will take care within
four months since its launch in January
2020 we have seen a surge in utilization
of this facility the app that was first
introduced to corporate customers in
witnessed an increase of more than 50
percent during the lockdown
among its this base so other the app is
being rolled out to our entire retail
customer base it will enable us to
explain our scope of wellness and other
value-added offerings to customers going
beyond addressing their insurance
purchase claim intimation and query
cells in each increasing with customers
beyond business critical in these times
we introduced several initiatives
including online business to help
customers pay positive cyber safe and
engage each of these sessions witness
participation of over 4,000 customers
further for corporate customers we
conducted focus sessions in involving
eminent professionals from the health
care space and our senior members to
discuss on relevant risk and insurance
aspects we reached out to more than
three and a half thousand corporate and
SME clients in the process
turning to our channel partners as you
know what diverse the solution set up
from the key component of our
competitive
strength over the years we've deployed
technology solutions we equip our
general partners with the right tools to
conduct business and service their
customers in these trying times ensuring
customer retention becomes an important
growth lever for our federal partners to
help them in their retention as such
we've deployed the latest technologies
called tools for example robocalling and
CRM tools for motor dealer partners you
also activated our remote work from home
call center for this purpose further we
have encouraged increased uses usually
of digital tools like Myra and I partner
for sourcing and servicing customers
while many of our partners are already
using these tools some of them require
handling these we have conducted
training programs for these partners to
familiarize them with these tools and
guide them to on other challenges being
faced timing then we are during this
lockdown more than four and a half
thousand channel partners have gained
from our online webinars conducted by
senior leaders it will remain at the
Munch when we run a focused campaign
called Iran for the SME segment this
year despite the contraint constraints
we have launched this initiative through
our multiple digital platforms
positioning it has digital run this
approach our alert results as we have
witnessed eighty-nine percent of
business sourcing through our digital
solutions during the lockdown for this
segment even as we work towards
supporting our customers and channel
partners we've been ensuring the safety
and well-being of our employees in fact
we have taken steps on this front in
early March much before the lockdown at
our key office setups we had introduced
social distancing norms the use of
sanitizers and deployed screening
equipment to monitor employee health as
we moved to a complete work from home
scenario post the national lockdown our
technology solutions and remotely
deployable IT infrastructure has helped
us in maintaining service continuity
today our employees have the right tools
to operate and collaborate with
colleagues across more than 250 branch
offices and virtual office locations
further we have been engaging with our
employees in multiple ways during this
time we accelerate our efforts towards
upscaling our implies by leveraging
technology platforms in this regard we
introduced in learning programs self
consumption videos and shielding life
training events over 3,200 learning
hours were consumed through e-learning
modules for
further employees were given access to
987 videos with 150 plus hours of
learning content on our video portal key
point for those requiring requiring
special assistance we have scaled up our
internal app platforms such as Sam to
learn which provides online counseling
while ensuring well-being and
productivity of our employees given the
unprecedented scenario the management
committee the senior-most you know
develop the organisation has decided to
forgo 50% of its annual bonus of FY 2020
and salary increment for fi 2021 in
order to contain the expense of
management and I should say lumbered we
have committed to support the efforts of
policy makers and the society in
containing the impact of the pandemic as
part of our CSR commitment we have
contributed to ICS a group support of
rupees 1 billion towards initiatives
aimed at curtailing kovat 19 impact this
includes contribution of 500 million to
being care case fund by a company as
well as voluntary salary donations by
our employees with contributions ranging
up to one month salary donation as well
amounting to 12 million further we have
introduced free covered 19 testing for
the underprivileged sections of the
society for this we have partnered with
reputed diagnostic grants in addition we
have provided you have personal
protection equipment or PPE in medical
to medical staff treating coordinating
patients at certain government hospitals
in high-impact cities like Mumbai I mean
our efforts Authority has been
forthcoming and has announced several
measured measures for the benefit of
policyholders and to ensure smooth
operations of insurers this includes
directing insurers to simplify claim
procedures ensuring claim authorization
within towards etc it is also ensured a
swift response to Product Approval
enabling insurance insurers like us to
introduce dedicated Kovan 19 solutions
in time for other the authority has been
instrumental in ensuring that insurance
is classified as an essential service I
would also like to touch upon a few
specific announcements by the regulator
the authority had notified on March 27
2020 that insurance companies shall
continue to charge the prevailing rates
for motor third-party liability
insurance covers from April 1 2020
onwards until further order is issued
this will impact being that
firstly for the currently further in
April 16 2020 the authority announced
further relaxation for payment of
premium on the inverse form of the
third-party and health insurance
policies they made till May 15 2020 what
the industry this could lead to
short-term impact on premium growth as
customers may choose to renew at a later
date
additionally subdued auto sales in the
last few quarters followed by temporary
shutting of Williams are expected to
impact new business sourcing it would
does be a challenge for the motor
insurance segment to maintain the
desired growth trajectory in effect 2021
pursuant to regulatory guidelines and
prudent management of financial
resources the Board of Directors have
not recommended final dividend for fi
2020 in this scenario the interim
dividend declared by the company will
become the final dividend for a SOI 2020
it is important for you to note that
despite the current meltdown we have
demonstrated a strong solvency position
of 2.1 seven times as at March 31st 2020
our solvency ratio continues to be well
above the regulatory minimum of 1.5
things let me now add you of the
industry performance in the recently
concluded fiscal year the general
insurance industry registered a growth
of eleven point seven percent in s5 2020
over effect 2019 the industry GDP moving
up from one hundred and one thousand
eight hundred ninety three point zero
two billion in s5 2020 from one thousand
six hundred ninety four point four eight
billion in FY 2019 as per GA council
report excluding crop segments this
growth would be ten twenty seven percent
the overall growth and growth excluding
crop segments was one point seven and
four point three percent respectively
for q4 2020 as compared to q4 to fight
2019 become minor issue for the industry
one hundred twelve point six percent in
nine months
FY 2020 as compared to one hundred and
thirteen percent so the overall combined
issue of the private multi-line general
insurers was one hundred six point five
percent in nine months
fi 2020 as compared to one hundred three
point four percent in nine month fi 2019
these numbers are based on available
public disclosures information published
on the respective company websites
excluding
national united the land sent and a
little milder coming to the outcome
filling your head it is extremely
difficult to gauge the exact economic
damage and consequent impact on our
industry at this point at this you know
as such you know giving a guidance at
this stage could be misleading having
said that I would still like to share
our current view of how different
segments could behave in the near term
now after the commercial lines are
concerned given the increase in rates
for some of the occupancies we expect
the fire cooks with port failure to grow
reasonably well
however marine and engineering segments
may witness be good due to reduced
transit assignments and delay in project
commencements we have also witnessed
policy extinctions
installments due to working capital rate
constraints group Health's penetration
should increase given the overarching
health concerns and the Ministry of Home
Affairs directive on workers we expect
rural segments to witness faster
turnaround post lockdown as the lockdown
is lifted idle times and stalled
construction projects may need to start
at risk or resumption we expect event
insurance credit and liability insurance
segments may see increased claims demand
for pandemic risk cover should rise as
it is current across people in order
prevalent covered in India as far as
little lines are concerned motor
portfolio growth would be would get
impacted due to subdued growth in new
vehicle sales
further influenced by the zero hike in
third-party previous rates still short
the intimation from the authority we
expect lower impact on agency and point
of sale based channels due to a higher
focus on renewal portfolio while we are
currently experiencing lower claim
incidence in motor portfolio there could
be a surge in claims once lockdown is
lifted further with regard to the retail
help indemnity portfolio we expect
subdued growth in q1 a frequently 21 in
particular we expect help agency should
grow during this period given our
efforts to build this network over the
last few years talking about the health
benefit portfolio we expect muted
disbursement in banking and we see an
HSE sector which may have an impact on
growth of the segment travel segment
demand would be most adversely impacted
on
the other hand we expect the SME channel
to continue exhibiting higher growth
give us move to digital adoption and
with the current challenging operating
environment we continue to reorient our
business model as we given unfolds even
though this you know through this
unprecedented situation the fundamentals
of a customer company remains strong we
are also preparing to underlying
opportunities that this event has
provided to us our focus will continue
to be creating value for all our
stakeholders through Prudential
Regulation harnessing technology and
pursuing sustain profitability for the
long term now in spite of the immediate
challenge we remain confident of the
wrong long term prospects for the
industry remains robust and in fact may
become even stronger than certain
segments our effort would be to
disproportionately benefit from any
long-term positive let me emerge for the
energy I will now request Gopal to take
you through these financial numbers for
the different is gone completed quarter
thanks for go find good evening everyone
hope everyone is staying safe and Hindi
I will now give you a brief overview on
the financial performance of the company
for the quarter and the area dreadmaster
t1 2020 we have put up the results
presentation on our website you can
access it as we walk you through the
performance numbers launched directly
Miam income of the company stood at
rupees 133 point one three billion in FY
2020 as compared to rupees one forty
four point eight billion in FY 19 ad
growth of eight point one percent
excluding the prop segment or GDP
increase to to face one thirty three
point zero two billion in fi 2020 as
compared to one twenty point three six
billion in FY 2019 resisting a growth of
ten point five percent this was in line
with industry growth excluding crop
signal the GDP growth was two point nine
percent in quarter for FY 2020 over
quarter for FY 2019 as compared to
industry growth of four point three
percent for the same period our GDP
growth was primarily driven by our focus
on preferred segments such as fires
health
motor marine and liability consequent to
the increase in minimum prescribed rates
for certain occupancies under fire
segments this segment registered as ltd
julia growth of forty two point nine
percent in FY 2020 thereby heating the
GDP growth of our property and casualty
segments as indicated in our results
presentation
overall property and casualty signal
grew by twenty point four percent in FY
2020 over FY 2019 on the retail side of
the business SME an agency channel and
health in divinity continue to grow
faster and remain our area of focus to
harness the potential of these segments
we have been expanding our distribution
network to increase penetration in title
3 and type 4 cities our individual ages
including the point of sale distribution
where forty seven thousand five forty
eight as on March 31 2020 as against
thirty five thousand seven twenty nine
as one master d1 2019 the long term
motor penetrations of private cars
increase to 19 percent for the period
ended March 31 2020 from three point six
percent for the period until mass 31
2019 and for two wheelers it's to Dec 15
quadric percent for the period hundred
mass 31 2020 from twenty eight point
eight percent for the period ended mass
31 2019 the advanced premium was
thirteen point two five billion as that
was 31 2020 from thirteen point two four
billion as at mass 31 2019 combined
ratio to ten hundred point four percent
in FY 2020 as compared to ninety eight
point eight percent in FY 2019 drive
only on account of long term motor
policies change in product mix and
losses from catastrophic events combined
ratio stood at hundred point one percent
in quarter for 2020 as compared to
ninety nine percent in quarter for FY
2019 our investment that six rows two
rupees to sixty three point two seven
billion at minus thirty one twenty
twenty as compared to rupees two forty
eight point four five billion at
December 31 2019
our investment leveraged net of boring
boring was four point two one times at
once thirty one twenty twenty as come
tied to four point one six times at
discipline thirty one twenty nineteen
investment income increased two rupees
eighteen point four seven billion in FY
2020 as compared to rupees 17.5 said
millionaires by 2019 on a quarterly
basis investment income decrease two
rupees four point zero six billion in
quarter four F by 2020 as compared to
the piece four point one four billion
quarter for FY 2019 in the national
income of quarter four F by 2020 and the
full year 2020 included impairment on
equity investment assets of rupees 100
two billion as per its policy consequent
to market volatility at the end of the
year resulting from uncertainty and
impact of covert 19 event our capital
games including the impairment of equity
investment assets was lower at rupees
one point nine nine billion in FY 2020
as compared to rupees four point two
five billion in FY 2019 capital gains
again including the impairment on equity
investment assets in quarter for FY 2020
was at a negative of rupees 0.25 billion
as compared to rupees point five six
billion in water for FY 2019 as a
company we have always exhibited tighter
internal exposure norms as against
regulatory limits on the fixed income
side we continue to focus on safety
liquidity and returns in that order of
priority given that we do have a large
friction come portfolio including
government securities accordingly we
have invested a high proportion
eighty 1.7 percent of the debt portfolio
in sovereign or triple a and about it
with security well that they have
focused on the quality of portfolio on
this front we have zero exposure of over
fixed income portfolio insecurity is
rated below EE we do not have a single
instance of delayed interest or default
over the last 19 years we will continue
to adopt a disciplined approach in terms
of the investment that we make our
profit before tax blue by six point two
percent to say rupees sixteen point nine
seven billion in FY 2020 as compared to
rupees fifteen point nine eight billion
in FY 2019
whereas profit before tech grew by seven
point three percent to rupees 3 point 7
1 billion in q4 2020 as compared to
replace three point four three billion
in q4 FY 2019 as taken in the previous
waters
earnings calls the company is elected to
exercise the option of lower income tax
rate the effective tax rate was twenty
nine point seven percent a left by
Twenty twenty and twenty three point
nine percent in quarter four F by 2020
consequently profit after tax grew by 13
percent to rupees nine eleven point nine
four billion in FY 2020 as compared to
the page ten point four nine billion in
FY 2019
whereas profit after tax grew by twenty
three point eight percent two rupees two
point eight million eight two billion in
quarter for 2020
as compared to his 2.2 million in
quarter for 2019 return on average
equity was 20.8% in FY 2020 as compared
to 2008 21.3% in FY 2019 the return on
average equity for water for 2020 was
eighty nine point eight percent as
compared to 17.5% in quarter for FY 2019
solvency ratio was two point one seven
times at 1:31 2020 as against two point
one eight times at December 31 2019
continued to be higher than the minimum
regulatory requirement of 1.5 times as
we conclude our address I would like to
summarize that we entered water for FY
2020 and the full year created 20 with a
diversified product portfolio healthy
financials the company continues to
focus on prudent underwriting while
improving this competitive positioning
further we remain focused on enhancing
our digital capabilities and drive the
agenda of sustainable growth I would
like to thank you all for attending our
own earnings conference call and we
would be happy to take any specific
questions that in the house thank you
very much we will now begin the question
and answer session anyone who wishes to
ask a question you may press star and
one on the touch-tone telephone if you
wish to remove yourself from the
question - you may press star and two
participants are requested to use
handset for asking a question ladies and
gentlemen we will wait for a moment
while the question - assembles the first
question is from the line of Silicon
patty from McQuarrie t-scores
yeah hi you know I know yeah hi Aditi so
you know I know it is a very very tough
environment and difficult to give any
title and the Resta will moving fast
here but if I were to really look at
your combined operating ratio
considering that there will be losses in
so far te and there is a certain
operating leverage in the motor business
how do you see the spanning of validity
would it increase some say 100 point
four percent directionally we just move
on to do 449 2021 or you think there is
a possibility that you can contain it
because current acclaim experience is
favorable right I mean because there are
no accident planes and stuff so can it
offsetting negative impact coming from
Kovac 19 yeah so this is a very tough
question to answer at this point in time
because as you rightly said there are
many moving parts and there are changes
that are coming in from waters that you
didn't anticipate ever in your planning
exercise having said that when we look
at our current view looking at the
situation today unless there are some
and uncertain surprises that we haven't
we couldn't anticipate on ballots given
those positives and negatives that users
articulated +48 off the water in terms
of some claims increases let me see if
that's the right the DB what happens
also the right now unloads on panels we
believe that we should be able to
continue to deliver on our objective of
keeping the combined around hundred even
for this year but as I said this is a
very difficult to give a righted it is
only you should look at this as our
estimate currently this estimate can
very easily change soon if the
underlying reality changes that we
haven't been able to anticipate a
solution and one more question is in the
group is where you are seeing a
reasonable amount of demand would you
really think this could be a profitable
product opposition because maybe at the
individual level of course the product
is far more profitable than really
focusing at a group level look if you
see what we've been doing relative to
the industry mix so if you see the
industries mix of health the composition
of groups a group health for the
industries roughly about 50% yeah which
is the corporate employer increasing
segment shade Lord than 50 many fortunes
on something for us that number is
roughly around 37%
which tells you that you know and you
not approach right so we're focusing on
we always focus on building a
sustainable portfolio so the early group
health has been a you know segment which
is being difficult in terms of pricing
in the market so the point is
immediately the point of your making
having said that in this environment one
should expect a bit more reasonable
approach and underwriting from the
marketplace if at all we find pricing
being sensible then we would look at it
if it is not then we will revenge the
cautious the way we've been operating
what we've been doing even when you're
looking at that share of the mix rate of
the work our approach has been go
granular focus on Vietnamese mid market
small clients not go for the big-ticket
you know policies from the FSI or for
writing of me which huge employee base
where the comparative pressure drives
the premium down to a level which is our
system so we not be in any way winning
any of this you know on cash and we have
deliberately you get the beaks for
others see with approach in the
philosophy will continue and we'll see
how it plays out in terms of X so in
terms of needed because of it that is of
course a bit of a modeling that we are
doing and like moving the models that
are floating around if it makes a lot of
assumptions on what will happen to the
number of people get infected in India
and there is that element of risk that
we are carrying okay and finally one
last question is on the investment book
you know I mean if you were to look at
globally the interest rates are really
happy when you know structure it looks
like it's going to be a very low
interest rate environment globally I
don't know how long it will be
sustainable in this environment you know
your ROA of course and always been
pretty good into any questions class
strange when that be addressed because
of structurally lower investment returns
considering the rate interest rate are
heading or likely to head in future so
this is being true even before this
event and you know we couldn't also have
a long debate on what this could do
macroeconomic Lee over a longer period
of time as the global supply can get
disrupted what it does to inflation
while it is obviously very rates down to
lower levels but it's again you know
very very speculative to estimate what
will happen to church one or two years
into the future
how has been moving
you see in cycles we would want to
continue to focus on delivering on the
are we if we believe that interest rates
are going down to a level which is not
sustainable we would want to improve the
combined of course depends on the market
condition in terms of become built of
intensity I think on competitive
intensity we believe this event could
potentially send them the stronger
simply because of throws the balance
sheets in the some of the companies have
built over the years the solvency
cushion that we have also the digital
leadership that we have in the market
but I think the point that we making
remains valid in any scenario today
which is very very unfair thank you
I remind you to the participants please
limit your questions to per participant
should you have any call of requestor to
rejoin the queue please the next
question is from the line of nari MW
from JP Morgan please go ahead yes thank
you for the opportunity and then thank
you so much for your the belly excellent
presentation
I have a two questions one about the
your technology side now it seems to be
the pretty tough time for the every
industry it means that the overall the
not only the marketing the claim and on
the writing probably barely child in the
bedroom
so the my question is how do you rate
the company's technology in both claim
adjustment and on the writing
constructed compared to the industry and
then the second question is about the
the specific underwriting
soft here so overall the underwriting
related with the factory insurance
probably relatively small but the the
quoted 19 finished via the major the
pandemic globally so I just want to know
whether any concern we should have
relate to their business interruption
coverage so any update on this
appreciated thank you okay let me do the
second one first and then I'll answer
the first questions on the second one
you know there are two types of BI
covers which you you know you know there
are
you know bi that triggers on our damage
material damage and there are non damage
bi which gets triggered without a
material damage like you know let's say
triggered by a pandemic in India there
is no NDVI that has policies in the
market so all the bi policies that we
write are with a trigger of a material
damage and pandemic is an exclusion so
contractually we don't see any risk we
I'm sure you are aware what is happening
globally on this matter but from a
contractual perspective we don't see a
risk coming to your first question I
think that's a great one and you know
honestly the way we see it is that some
of the capabilities that we built I
talked about the sourcing side in terms
of the fact that today we launched you
know for the sa means this visit two big
months of you know policy procurement
and we could launch our initiative which
we do you know every year as a digital
initiative and 89% of policies we've
source digitally and the SME business
has grown in this period and that
probably tells you the digital
capability that we've built on the
claims side and that's probably the most
important arresting aspect that you've
talked about there are lots of elements
that we've built on the retail side we
keep talking about I talked about the
inspect the you know visual the virtual
in you know inspection that we do today
as of now in this lockdown phase one
hundred percent of motor claims that are
getting paid or you are getting settled
are using you know that capability
similarly the AI based in a health
insurance claims but on the corporate
side you know this has been a period
where we've done a lot of innovative you
know work and I'll talk about a couple
of them and I will then ask a look to
add anything that we may want to add so
on the on the risk inspection side we've
started virtual risk a you know
assessment we you know we are doing a
video based risk assessment virtually
without having to send our risk
inspection inspectors in we are
providing remote risk advisory on plant
operation we have a team of specialists
who provide risk advisory we are doing
that remotely we provide
io2 IOP based monitoring tools and not a
very large number of customers who use
some of these solutions but the ones
that are using it are getting triggers
sitting at home so similarly you can you
know drone base north survey in this
period to help customers I look you have
anything else that you want going yeah
apart from the value-added services that
you mentioned on the claim side what we
have done is on the basis of virtual
documents we have started settling came
here have been reducing the backlog of
claims tremendously just to give you a
sense of the number of policies for exam
in this log down period using the chat
water the email what do you know what do
we call it the ERP a solution that you
have able to issue more than forty
thousand policies and these are
corporate policies I think that's very
clear so just want to confirm so are you
very optimistic on the company's the the
democracy of gaining or the the market
positioning after cope in nineteen
because that the experience for example
China Korea and other many developed the
market this is strong the innovation
seems to give a more opportunity for the
for the company so I'm just want want to
get some color how the management to
think about the company's future after
the Kobe nineteen then we given very
little optimistic relative to the other
players in the market they said we are
you know definitely cautious of what we
larger environment and what it will do
to the economic growth and consequently
insurance business but within that as I
said right to my opening address we
should be able to benefit
disproportionately because of some of
these coins that we made innovation
technology capability as also balance
sheet set
take it so much that's very clear
appreciate thank you the next question
is from the line up should I ask you any
from c-elysee India Private Limited
please go ahead I thank you for the
opportunity so I had one question
regarding so so there was a nadir I give
initiation but there was a committee set
up which is going to talk about
indemnity based health products to be
sold by life insurers as well so I want
to understand how how this will impact
their general insurance industry or iti
Lombard as such specifically and you see
because of this the price competition
going ahead and you know the product
becoming less competitive for you guys
to keep growing at the in it the way
you've been growing also second thing
which I wanted to understand because you
have a good company which is also doing
which is which which will get a license
to do indemnity health if I die approves
it how does that affect like what kind
of you throw some light on that how does
that affect your group strategy etc so
the left knee probably on to the third
one first because that's separate from
the response to the rest you know
wherever there are segments of business
where we have similar products like for
health benefit we compete in the
marketplace and that's how it is and if
this happens in the in every side we
would also compete in the marketplace we
wouldn't worry about that coming back to
the larger question that you're asking
yes the committee has been formed but
the committee I as far as I know
couldn't meet because of all of this I
don't believe their meeting has happened
unless in this period a virtual meeting
has happened that I'm not aware of so
the committee has to come together and
give the report we'll have to wait for
the report the committee is if you
having said that why we don't know what
the committee will say if you step back
till about 2015-16 there was no such
separation the live companies were
allowed to
right you know all types of health and
in fact we as an industry we as a
company wanted to the right long-term
health which we were not even allowed to
at that point in time the separation
came at that funny time it wasn't as if
in those days also the lies companies
were doing a lot of help indemnity
business and let me get into the the
elements of their business as I said if
you look at the overall health business
roughly fifty percent now almost fifty
percent of business comes from group end
now in group health typically we offer a
bouquet of solutions to corporates which
has fire which has marine which has
liability and we offer you know that
bunch now logically there shouldn't be
any big competitive advantage that a
health a life company may have unless
they want to undercut further you know
that is one Arian if they want to do
that that's a better choice but
generally we wouldn't expect that to be
a festival strategy so large part of the
volume of business comes from group
health and we as an industry have scaled
up that you know that business including
managing the you know using that slow to
manage the network and the other thing
that you have to realize is the portion
distribution capability there has to you
have to have many other capabilities on
the health side to be able to compete be
it in terms of in-house claims services
and you know we took claim service
in-house in 2008 there is some
capability and technology advantage that
we build for example the IBM solution
that I talked about you can start
writing helping challenged on the retail
side using a TPA but I don't know if
that really helps in terms of building
these capabilities so that's that's
number one and number two if you see the
approach that we are taking even if
let's say like company to come in they
opposed that we are taking if you see
what we've been talking about earlier
I'll take care is really taking health
insurance to another level of providing
complete solution - you know people so
for example in this lockdown period on
the I'll take a nap we have a feature
for our corporate lands where you can do
a Tele consultation with doctors and we
have a dedicated you know a partnership
which you know delivers it that
you've now opened up for all our
customers you don't necessarily have to
be a health customer and that's you know
really picked up even at this point in
time but these are capabilities that
we've built over the over the years in
terms of network in their ecosystem
because of technology in terms of data
analytics if someone is able to come in
and compete so be it we wouldn't really
worry about that competition having said
that we don't know if the regulator will
allow it we'll have to wait for the
committee report okay thank you so much
thank you the next question is from the
line of Jeannie Hsieh from NK global in
his cohort
yeah hi Andy
I just wanted to confirm the kind of I
mean I look great a little further on
your opening remarks and you talked
about the good features work quit from
individual segments from fired and also
get a little bit a little a little
detail into it but why you say that you
know why you expecting a fire to grow
well whereas my right to go around and
all so that segment if we can elevate
once again a little put Andy Taylor
granularly that would be really helpful
yeah we can I can do that in a regular
manner but it'd still be very difficult
to predict or give any guidance on where
we see the numbers for obvious onions so
if you look at the corporate income the
largest segments are fired where you had
price increases during this year and
last year and corporate customers
generally don't want to keep their
assets are insured so the b2b segment I
think largely will be protected now
within that fire will should grow I
should have a positive growth this year
the rest of it is a bit of a uncertain
you know picture because for example
marine transit which is what you you
know where you ensure you know the large
16 that obviously is stalled as of now
now how do we predict a number if you
don't know when you know a red zone will
become an orange and when an orange zone
will become green so you're even ready
the planning for number
on a day-to-day basis we are reviewing a
very very frequently you know internally
within our teams having said that we
probably couldn't anticipate this
extension this quarter you know there in
this month now we don't know what will
happen 15 days from now so very
difficult to give you a sense of what
people um burrs will be for the year
what we've decided is that we will watch
it I mean every part of our business we
are basically looking at what is
happening on a daily basis we've
completely changed our dashboards of
monitoring the business in this period
right from even before we went in to
work from home as a whole company we
realized that you know this is a big
change that is happening so we
completely change our dashboard so all
we are doing is staying very close to
the ground to see what is happening and
reacting to it in terms of in terms of
seeing any opportunity that we that we
see so but on balance what we are saying
fire we think will be positive marriage
would be negative you know engineering
would be negative now extent of
negatives we can say for this quarter
definitely negative thereafter we don't
know liability you know and afterwards
the two key ones my ability at it should
be okay motor and help help should do
well though in this quarter it may be a
bit slow but overall for the year it
should do okay do reasonably okay motor
will be affected it depends on when you
know dealerships are open and in vehicle
sales comes now again on new vehicles
and this as you know you know two months
from now the whole country is being
opened up and dealerships are open can
you predict with any level of confidence
the customer psyche at this point in
time there are two quantity points of
view some of you understand the auto
sector as well you know one segment
believes that there will be no more
adoption of personal mobility so people
will use vehicles more and so people may
buy more vehicles at least the lower end
there is another point of view that you
know the the amount of travel itself
will come down so and people won't have
discretionary spending ability so they
were not actually buy cars either one of
them can happen and anyone who predicts
I think is
wouldn't predict with any benefit
because of being in the past if you know
there is an opportunity thank you and we
things I could hear the question could
you just repeat that I'm Ching with te
kahui deviant would provide Dini
tail drinks or danger to you over a
period of time
and haven't you read musico teeny art or
the whole of the business they've done
the comedy range is a strategy so you
know we believe this will be in the
long-term orbital for the GI events like
this make people more aware of the risks
that we have it's unfortunate that's the
nature of our industry but when things
like these things happen if you realize
the importance of risk management and
protection so in DeLand particularly if
you look at the health insurance you
know space
even when shall happen post that in Hong
Kong health insurance you know demand
went up naturally
so one balance we believe this will be
positive for the je industry in a medium
term in the short term it will be really
it god of the top line will disappear
because I think all companies right now
must be doing at this stage particularly
given by motor in terms of approach
Restless what we're trying to do is we
are we are enabling all our the entire
part of our organization and the
extended arm which is our distributors
to enable them to do as much of business
as they can from from home using tools
using training etcetera that we're
talking about and actually we are kind
of opening up a bit more segments to do
business than what we were earlier
willing to particularly in let's say
motor insurance you know even healthier
you know going very very focused in
terms of scaling of the business
particularly to the internal etcetera so
it's not a big change in segments of
business but the focus is in terms of
the renewal the old book and how do we
get a higher share of the market using
our digital capabilities Sanjeev you
want to add anything more to what I just
said
no absolutely right I also just to
mention before last we had added virtual
offices across the country and that does
hold a health is good even in the the
month which is just gone by April a drop
is there but relatively low and it's
still somewhat of activity in those
regions so we will early you what your
search stated well we we extensive
physical to reach also that we had
created two virtual offices across the
conceivable olders good and the time to
come now okay
and secondly a father is the fixed
income in the equity ratio of the total
investment Pope is on 31st December the
99 31st March 2004 Polly will take that
yeah sure so I think on the equity book
I think that cost
on 31st December 2019 the holding would
be about 10% of the overall investments
will be into equity set cost that number
at the end of 31st March 2020 is at
about ten point nine percent so roughly
eleven percent or so and the rest of the
book is largely split on a lot well
primarily on the fixed income portfolio
between government securities and
corresponds and that number would be I
think from the market value perspective
which is what we mentioned as a part of
the opening remarks if you would have
looked at the master market impact on
the equity portfolio as at the reporting
date and I'm giving this number before
the provision for the impairment that we
took on the equity assets the master
market loss on the equity portfolio is
roughly about finding 50 crores I said
that reporting data but we don't
directly help I do mostly very clear we
don't we keep some money in liquid funds
but we also you know largely use the
crêpes market but all the fixed income
positions will directly hit little bit
exposure is some liquid funds little bit
here in this angle asking over the
period of times one of the participants
are here arc when they do think envision
it looks person that over a period of
time they will diminish many 56 return
on equity we do not consider a bottom of
course including combined ratio that you
answered including equity allocation in
the top on the investment book you know
absolutely if you see we've been kind of
reducing our equity allocation of excuse
me over the last three four years in a
sense we were a bit concerned about the
valuations and in this period in the
month of March early April we increased
allocation a little bit but the market
ran up
faster than what we expected again we
don't know if this is sustainable but
you guys will know that better than us
but we would want to increase equity
allocation what we are doing is we are
certain so we keep evaluating certain
companies that we like and if it comes
within our range of price we you know
increase our allocation it's not as if
we ever fixed you one that we want to
increase it to X percentage we go stock
specific and actually in this period we
increase the elevation a little bit not
to the extent that we would have liked
to but we've increased the allocation so
we would do that the other point to
remember is even in this period when the
market pulls up in the Mun in March
some extremely high-quality corporate
names yields went up tremendously and
that was a period where we even on the
fixed income side we talked in some of
these you know high-quality corporate
names and even from a duration
perspective we just added some little
bit there and that I believe is going to
help us in the long term what you have
to realize is that it is the incremental
book let's assume that the interest rate
you know stays at 6%
you know for thing is and let's say you
know triple a spread in this 50 pixel
square extremism whatever it is it's the
incremental flow that we have doing list
at that level the old stock remains we
since the rate comes down we have a
large mark to market positive I mean if
we would have a large mark to market
positive on the bond side we would
decide if you want to take those profits
or this basis view of that we have in
terms of interest changes and we've
generally been contrarian I mean you
know what a year and a half back where
everyone was saying interest rates will
go through the roof oil etc we went long
and that called played out so again at
this point in time I would be foolish to
predict where it is going to go one year
from now but we will watch it very
closely and we will take the right
course but it is equally in the sample
return capsule but finally fall out
request her to rejoin the queue piece I
reminder to the participants please
limit your questions to doper
participant should he have any follow-up
requests to really join the few piece
the next question is
Delana by Jaques rhetoric from being a
securities please go ahead
thank you dr. Gerson sir the commission
payout systematically for the water so
what road I'm sorry what winter I
couldn't get you Commission Commission
Commission Gopal you have the answer so
jokes I think it is early I think if
you're referring to the are you
referring to the net commissioner issues
yeah also so when you look at the next
next Commission ratio I think a Jaques
is obviously a function of one
what kind of business mix that you write
across the portfolio of businesses that
we write one in that you know kind of
split the net commissions in terms of
commissions paid which is what we kind
of incurred for sourcing businesses and
the second element is more of an income
that accrues to us which is by virtue of
the reinsurance commissions that we own
with respect to the portfolio that we
will be doing in terms of the risk
transfer now in this quarter when you
look at when you look at the breakdown
insofar as the Commission paid or let's
say that position the issue is concerned
there is not much of a moment in terms
of what you see but in quarters for what
s what we explain as a part of the
opening remarks some of the health
benefit portfolio is something that we
have not seen as much growth as what you
would have expected it to be and that
part of the business is something that
we kind of also we have been
historically reassuring and to that
extent the extent of the Commission
income that we would have earned on that
part of the business is relatively
lowered so hence when you look at the
overall net Commission to issue it looks
like there has been an increase but
insofar as the acquisition cost is
concerned it is there is not any
significant change that's one and
secondly I think what we have always
kept looking at is more from a combined
perspective because that would be a true
reflection of the overall operations of
insurance that we had right and there if
you'd have seen whether it is for the
quarter for or whether it is for the
full year in line with what we have been
articulating
also in our earlier
years as well as a part of our calls you
should try and sustain the overall
combined it around 100% and on rainy
wills so different life like motor and
health at least what the portion is or
how much is Remy well nobody want to
give the number so again if you're
looking at your let's say for the hair
motor site for example if you look at
roughly we would last year we would have
had almost a 50/50 kind of mix for the
full year 2019 new would have been 50%
and renewal would have been 50% for the
current year by 20 given that the new
vehicle sales have been relatively lower
in terms of growth not extensive
proportion of new trade even so new is
about 38% and the renewal will be able
to shoot opposite and one help and on
the health part of the business I think
given the fact that I think we were
almost there
one of the things that we would have to
look like on the health side for example
on the internet each side when you look
at the overall internal T growth for
health the new health ingenuity growth
which is what we have also put on
reservation paper deck that's one area
we are significantly focusing on over
the last three to four years and the new
health indemnity growth has grown by
about 69 percent and should have looked
at better because that's what I
relatively small and base which is why
the number looks to be the overall
health portfolio again on the ability
side thrown by reports 37 percent the
renewal book has grown at about 17
percent so sorry to interrupt sir but
showing a follow up request to take each
and akiles
thank you the next question is from the
line of Nitish
from invested capital please go ahead
thanks Liam this the fear also I think
we have seen this entity releases last
year also we saw good readable uses so
when we are looking at by a fully F
opportunity how should we look at this
result is
and whether we should expect them to be
sustainable in future look really
exactly you know obviously depend on our
actual analysis that we keep carrying
out monthly and quarterly but the
principle remains the same when we I
think opal has been talked about to
Union this over the over there you know
quarters in it we when we reserve we are
conservative or deserving and because we
don't know how whether all our
assumptions will play out and that's a
tight oppose that most you know quality
reinsurance companies do across the
world and over the periods if the actual
trend proves to be in line with or
rather better than what we had
anticipated we would have had some
reduces so if you look at our reserve
reasons we would exact one term we can
never predict that next year give me so
much but you should continue to have
some of the visibility continue with the
same strategy and our strategy the
conservatism in terms of reserving
hasn't changed shortest straw'
unexpectantly
going into the next year our top ten
growth may remain slightly subdued in
that environment how much flexibility we
have come out pretty expensive ected and
also we have seen a dissenter expense of
management education which you have to
do some share on their accounts which
link that probably in some time of
businesses we were not able to tax was
higher than what regulatory require yeah
so the second one is gopal to answer but
in terms of the first one if you see the
the crew fixed cost and you know if you
look at the expense ratio there is a
distribution cost which is the
commission that we pay and a true
operating cost which is the innocence
fixed nothing is fixed but that is kind
of fixed cost if the top line and that
number is actually you know kind of a
single-digit number the the the
operating cost so if you see the element
of the sourcing cost if a top line goes
on that will also go down for us also
what we are doing is we are looking at
all our costs to the fine-tooth comb and
we believe from the longer-term
perspective obviously right now we are
going through a certain phase
we believe there are huge learnings that
we got out of this you know and last one
month experience which we would want to
continue to leverage in you know as we
go along you would want to become a
hundred percent digital company we would
want to have 50 percent of our employees
work from home even in the foreseeable
future so these are things that we are
kind of working on and we are working on
those plans for future it may not have
an immediate benefit in terms of
operating cost but in the longer term it
should give us some leverage but
honestly for us we out of the combined
ratio that part is a relatively small
part as I explained there are real large
number in these claims ratio and the
distribution cost gopala if you want to
add anything to that and answer the
second question sure I think I'll answer
the second question I think when you
look at as a company we have always
wanted to ensure compliance to
regulations insofar as extensive
management is concerned so in that
regard as a company we have been an
absolute compliance to the regulatory
requirement which is on an aggregate
basis where they extract every company
to be within those limits on expense of
management but your point is correct
there is always an element of experience
allocation that happens across sub
segments which is also what is laid down
by regulation and as for the requirement
if in any of the sub segments basis the
allocation of expenses that happens to
each of those lines of businesses in
case if there is any subsequent that
exceeds the limit that is laid down to
that exchange the excess of those
extensions is required to be borne out
of the shareholders fund and that is
exactly what we have done but on an
aggregate basis as a company the attempt
has being always to make sure that we
are in compliance with the overall limit
that has been laid down and so for its
technicians are concerned and just to
add on I think one other point which is
something that we have spoken about also
on the in deepest just track to what
Barco said one should also be equally be
mindful of the fact that when it comes
to fixed costs one of the things that we
have been telling over the last couple
of quarters in particular is the
acquisition of the crm platform that we
did in quarter 3 and now that obviously
entails some element of fixed cost in
the form of depreciation
that kind of comes through all what runs
water but the impact in terms of revenue
this is the expectations that we'd
already factored in as a part of buying
the chair and platform that would happen
over a period of three to four years now
in that regard the platform that we work
with acquired in what regime again has
been kind of progressing very well in
terms of the expectations that we would
have said yes in fact in these times of
uncertainties you have actually been
able to deploy that CRM platform quite
effectively and we have been able to do
it when we kind of also indicated as a
part of the introductory remarks that we
have been able to do a lot of
robocalling and other related aspects to
ensure continuity of customers for
renewability of their policies we have
actually been able to use this platform
to our advantage and you want to add to
what this book was just said about that
one so absolutely the openings of
platform have been a great boon to us
and when you picked up in October it was
more of you know from our insistence
reviews for the dealer and offer this
platform in the current situation is
created I even built among whom they
said they also want mr. B installed
we'll be happy to note that in April
when actually you know things have done
excess they've been able to activate
almost sixty seven dealers become part
of the platform so we are really excited
and it should go a long way in terms of
strengthening our relationship with the
dealers as well as helping them to reach
out their customers for the renewals
which will be the key thing at least for
quarter one in a big way thank you the
next question is from the line
appreciation John Walla from ISL
please go ahead yeah and for the
opportunity couple of questions one is
can you elaborate what is the policy
regarding you know recognition of a
proxy impairment because if we really
look at it you know at 120 Kroll's
almost five percent of what your equity
book would have been as of the end of
you squatters so if it spread across
just you know is it only regarding one
stock
you know how do you hug you arrive at
that and what are the chances of that
recovering back and secondly on the
health side you mentioned that because
of your probably shift from benefit to
Indiana T the reinsurance Commission's
have come off
is this something which is tactical for
the short term or should we take it as a
as a long term trend and as a result you
know the overall profitability on that
segment could be under pressure
considering you know there was pretty
heavy the Insurance Commission that we
used to receive so let me answer the
first one and and I will cover a bit of
the second one ask Sanjeev to elaborate
on that in terms of the impairment we
have a policy this is a requirement but
we have a policy as a matter of prudence
where we paced for impairment when there
is a substantial fall in market price of
security below our acquisition cost now
this is obviously something that
happened in the month of March when the
market fell as much as it did and we do
an assessment whether the fall in price
is temporary permanent whether there is
a online change in the intrinsic value
of the of the investment of the
investing company and if we believe that
it is prudent to take kind of impairment
to to reflect the change in the fair
value of the investment company or
investing company then we take an
impairment as a matter of prudence
we need not but we do that so that's
something that we tested this time and
it's not one company there are a few
companies that we've taken a call on and
adjust the value to what we believe is a
fair idea now it is not as if we believe
so if you believe that a stock is you
know in a sense something that will not
deliver returns in the future we would
exist as you sell and exit and you know
maybe gradually we've done that over
even during the year we existed some of
the print media stocks we took the loss
and it took it because we didn't see a
future there
but these are not stars that we believe
that we will not get returns in the
future so we've taken a prudent it's a
put in producer you call in terms of
taking that hit now in terms of the
second question that you have you know
obviously it's not a tactical call to
shift out of benefit we like the benefit
business but you know as I think opal
explained that the NBC disbursements
have went down in the last water and
it's been down for a fair period and
hence the amount of business that we got
from our NBC partners we're relatively
lower but we are growing that visited
else in Alaska needs to explain that to
you okay clearly I mean we love benefit
for the business and it should be market
leaders in that particular segment we
would love to grow that but
unfortunately for last 18 months also
mentioned you know nvac sector has gone
through a bit of tightness in terms of
disbursement and that has impacted it
the one initial speculation bank is a
bank where deliver see we were able to
grow our business them in a very
reasonable face for this fall in the
embassy said we'll very sharp
we are diversifying we are keen on doing
new tires we have done few critical tie
ups on the banking side also last year
so we will continue to exploit you or
put you on the signal and as in
Manhattan on happens our relationship is
very thick with our partners and we will
get rolling on that front also I'm just
quickly on you know so clearly we are
seeing right now right now loss ratios
in motor segment going down
substantially in during the lockdown and
on the other hand you know we have also
seen the regulator of owning the hike in
motor TP
for the caning being you just want you
to understand I mean how do you see that
play out at least for this year and do
you intend to reconsider your you know
the inflation that you make in for motor
TP provisioning for this year so we will
have to watch the noble thing you know
it's a great question that you're asking
and you know this is something that our
actual team will evaluate you know
an ongoing thesis and obviously being
Curt claims dropped to a level that it
you know in drops and scales down they
would have factored some of that into
the assumptions but it's really it's
very difficult to predict what will
happen when things start reopening as I
said there are you know very very
logical and rational views on both sides
in terms of where the people will use
this well use vehicles more because of
personal mobility to rather than taking
public transport and will greatly
increase claims the jury is out will
have to watch the numbers and then take
a call but if it stays down we believe
the the actual team will address some of
this all day thank you so much thank you
the next question is from the line of
jamesha from our WC partners please go
ahead yeah I think two questions one is
could you talk a bit on the government
regulation of compulsion has get
insurance and how do you think that pans
out for you and the industry also you
know in terms of you know filling that
kind of queries you get from companies
especially on this inside there you are
strong and they're probably not kind of
covered that question one the other
pressure was more on kind of I want you
to understand the consumer psychology
yeah
you want the Cova type in product quite
early you know who I inquire who were
the buyers existing customers how was
this kind of you know being kinda spread
eventually that could kind of give you a
lot more kind of thought process on you
know personal individual health care
kind of as well yeah yeah I think so if
you want to take the two questions on
the SME and the recovered experience
clearly child apply the core big one
first
clearly when we launched this probably
was pretty early when things started you
know building up from a new perspective
where we held office is coming up
except I said you very good you have
followed two strategy family one is be
to be another it be to be
see there we've also gone and offered
this options from the cooperation of the
SMEs who won't take a cover the
employees and their family they was so
in a much bigger way to welcome people
we go see play they'll get join hands
with me players were in the online
stream and they are the ones who are
offering it to their customers the
initial response has been very very
encouraging but I must say that we also
are very closely looking in terms of the
distribution so that we don't have a
concentrated portfolio coming up so
we've done all our cuts and balances but
so far the acceptance and quite
naturally I am sure each one of us will
agree that anything on coverage said it
comes in because it's the imminent risk
evidently we all know day-to-day basis
it becomes a very very practical way to
take a cover on that while I must also
say the normal and then need to cover
which each of the customer has they are
also covered expenses in case of
hospitalization fully covered on the
essentials and if just one repeats at
one point to explain what he said so
we've given it to B to B to C or B to B
so as to eliminate adverse selection
risk and we are also monitoring the
portfolio diversification across the
country so that we don't get into any
concentrated pockets send you over t
okay yeah thanks
and also SME said in terms of this
compulsory health coverage typically on
an ongoing basis we do know that the
smaller GHI coverage at the group health
of Ages have been far more you know
beneficial for the company suddenly I
was able to provide our expression
service which is created for even larger
corporation SME we have been going for
doing that portfolio at a reasonable
pace of 25 percent we do believe that
any progression corporate and in which
they should end up our sink repeal so
this should be for the demand coming and
we will keep investing it but as valid
also nation initially we have complete
clarity that we will pick up this
business if it makes commercial sense if
this tremendous rate ba we will firmly
abstain from participating in that sort
of a business okay are you seeing any
inquiries children on that that you want
to just touch up from your corporate
segment on that on the so the worker
policy that the government has made it
compulsory from the Ministry of
we are seeing increasing queries and
they are from the medium sized and large
corporate especially from construction
side there are a lot of employees and a
few policies have been converted and
they are the people who are going back
into construction of projects and they
have workers in those areas working but
one more point I want to add is that
most of the comfort of people who are
employing workers have an es ie cover
which is applicable for four people only
a two-piece 21,000 or below so but that
most of the GSI hospitals don't have Co
with the facilities so therefore probit
only product also they can take for
people who have a IDF I cover for the
workers okay
just on the on the Kovac 19 for the
buyers on kind of you know non b2b to be
kind of you know new customers or
largely kind of existing customers kind
of you know talking about what number so
this typically would be our own sting
SME customers or corporate customers who
have been dealing with us we have been
in relationship over last few years but
the other part the benefits policies
that we take this policy that we are
selling through digital platforms
because this is going to a segment which
is probably below our current customer
base these are probably new customers
yes so B to B to C would be new custom
yes yes the B to B - B - B may be
existing customers who would have some
other relationship with us okay thank
you Thank You Jamie
the next question is from the line of
Malaga from HDFC security schemes go
ahead
hi good evening thank you for taking my
question
a number one or you know on the existing
benefit policies that we've written
would they kind of get triggered with
akavit 19 case and what is our risk
assessment on that so what sort of
reinsurance do we have
how well are we covered out there thank
you want to touch up on that and then
I'll add to it a final point current
benefit benefit structure the polishes
everyone done in the past
Kovach means fundamentally don't get
shaken on that there's clearly good the
instances are very well lifted and and
that one of them and we actually had
done the policy there was nothing like a
coronavirus of it which could have been
a penis or baby parties are also in
future how does it value involves we
will see it as it comes
but as of now someone must approve it
covered later public benefit policy we
spoke about it and our normal in the
mythical policy if any customer has it
they're fully covered in terms of
medical expenses on that so just track
towards and you said our benefit
policies usually have specific illnesses
that are covered in them these are
critical in this policies order at a
point in time and these are we insured
with some of the global leaders in
reinsurance okay but also I want to add
to what we just said in terms of your
question on risk I mean these are the
imponderables and you know which we
can't predict I mean if suddenly there
is some regulatory pressure to pay for
these claims you're not payable those
are things that we cannot pay rate as of
now but they should not be able say
these are not covered right right and
how our motor renewals behaving so far
you know from last week of March until
now you would have a TP book and only
book which would be reviewing what is
customer behavior being on there
so there is slight drop in retention
numbers but we've seen for the month of
March over the last few days we've seen
a small drop in retention but even in a
Phil we've seen a small drop Alice and
if to elaborate on it but week on week
we are seeing improvement sandy if you
want to add Oh clearly it from that
perspective one regulator has given
dispensation and continuity benefits to
the policies which are following jus
between de logged on here
but some of them could be you know too
many the one cash to have their foot
there you know renewals but that being
said yes in marginal drops you go it
channel widespread to put across just in
slightly more you know shopper drop on
the dealer said because they themselves
on on that even we are using various
technology based option like Ottomans I
mean the clear to get things view who
remove calling or with McCollum on the
agency side it's been even better
because the agents are able to follow up
and then you know push this customers
into the region digital more to you know
do the renewals but yes Elvira said
there has been a marginal drop but a
matter of time before it will come in
because there is a requirement also one
more thing on the TP shine which I must
mention that any new policy that the
sold over last year we're all long-term
so the TP any which way is covered by
nog and only view the old a part
which needs to be removed
that's it from Memphis thank you thank
you
the next question is from the line ups
and kiplyn from spot capital please
cover it thanks for the opportunity
that's the gist of what it was it
something more people auspicious how do
you probably actually have seen point
five of the fourth affiliate for just
wanted to say that if exceptionable I
believe it is largely because of the
Cretan contribution of believer then
then it changes to clean then thing do
you think this eighty four point five
hundred other people location personable
Omaha and depends the prospective party
- wanted to understand you want the
minimum code table which I think you
exchange the based on the morning show
the vehicle from what is this - what
actually film that could be an impact on
our overall typically go polymeric
question number one
yeah sure bloggers so I think circuit I
think I would approach to underwriting
the risk is something that we have been
talking about for the last so many
quarters yes
the lawsuit issues appear is clearly a
function of what kind of a mix that we
write in terms of private car
two-wheeler and commercial vehicles one
of the things that you should be equally
be mindful of is also the point that we
may mention which is with respect to for
fi twenty one so far
there is no rate hike that is being
proposed so doing nothing that by itself
will kind of push up the tipping loss
ratios for the overall industry and even
for the portfolios let me write
obviously it will have an impact insofar
as a loss ratio numbers are concerned
having said that I think what we have
tried to do over the years is to capture
the opportunity of the business mix
which we think are appropriate at
different points of time and that in
each of those occasions we have
recalibrated the mix depending on the
pricing environment that operated and in
that regard if you have same pot or
possibly the mix of business that we
write of the overall motor between
private car two-wheeler and commercial
vehicles I have undergone a significant
change even over the last couple of
years I mean you would have seen those
mixes then would have announced results
let's say in March 18 the mix of those
three segments was very different as
compared to the mix of boosters that you
would have seen for March 19 and even if
when you look at it for the current year
I think the mix of business would be
slightly different so in that sense
obviously it's a function of what kind
of pricing and dramatic operates and
within that we will continue to be this
selective on the mix that we would want
the kind of underwrite and keep looking
for opportunities so that we're able to
try and sustain the overall
profitability objective that we have set
for a pump for our choice as a company
and that's the way one would look at
their house associations good the
playthrough okay yeah you can change the
PPO based on deep non-insured very cool
this wanted to understand whether if in
fact about business or if you can make
it shorter so there again I think if you
look at the parent obligation I think
purely is purely a function of the value
of the premium that you write and again
there are been defined formula this is
which the quota is determined and on
that basis you are expected to write a
particular volume of business in order
to meet meteor code objectives insofar
as the new norms are concerned I think
the working group has submitted their
report and rightfully so if you were to
look at in that context I think the
thought process of moving the quota
based on the number of policies and then
of course there is also a factor of the
strength of the uninsured vehicles which
is also that one has to consider is
something in that sense I think in the
right direction
which would ensure that a larger section
of the motor vehicle owners are taking
an insurance policy something that has
been a challenge for the industry as a
whole so in that sense when you look at
it the new guidelines that has come to
as a part of the working group
recommendation it is definitely a step
in the right direction obviously we will
have two bases that recalibrate the mix
of business that we have to kind of
right between those private car
two-wheeler and commercial vehicles and
ensure that we are in compliance with
the norms compact initial working do
suggest that we need to dramatically
change our make sure that we comply with
a formula I it's all a function of as I
said what kind of mix will that entail
as I said you need to kind of strike a
right balance between all the three
segments whether it is private car to
will or commercial vehicles oh so this
one broader question when he said that
maybe the stronger companies will gain
market share the course post could then
then stimulus in the end effect of each
segment you think the market share green
could happen and whether you could see
again any competition in those segments
which you do maka shared link could
happen basically so you know this some
of the segments that we've seen this and
we've been talking about this shift in
any case without this current event
we've been saying that gradually market
share will shift to the stronger
companies and some of the segments we've
seen that play through so if you see
even this year in certain segments which
let's say for example fire segment we're
pricing went up last year our market
shares increase from roughly about nine
point three percent 29.8%
engineering market share increase so as
we said in the commercial lines in
definitely market share should increase
in the SME segments given what we just
talked about you know over this call in
terms of scream service also the market
share showed increase you increase
market share in motor damage you now
become the number one company known
damage again
because of some of these strengths that
we've built and incrementally we are
seeing faster growth in the health
segment in the last maybe about two
years and cope I'll give the number for
indemnity growth for this quarter
no significantly higher than the market
so we expect even their Mukesh gains to
come through I think that the point is
you more generic I mean if you see you
know the overall mix if you see the
private sector coming earlier we used to
talk about you know between the private
and public mukesh a movement that you've
seen but our sense is if you see even in
private sectors you know depending upon
how where people are and how the market
plays out in terms of claims etcetera
there are certain pressures that are
developing we will see if that leads to
some little benefit for us definitely in
a sec because of balance sheet
technological capability and the fact
that you've been able to manage this you
know Englishman is in this period we
should see some benefit that would be a
little okay lost precious can we do
based on Google Group other people could
benefit based and retail if it is
possible and vis-a-vis the what happens
even at the last year so broadly from
Kate I think when you look at the
overall yield portfolio I think what we
have also been talking about in terms of
loss ratios behavior I think contra tilt
will fundamentally as a business line
will have exhibited a high loss ratio
that is broadly remained at about 93 94
percent well whether you look at fi 19
or whether you look at fi 20 and
inherently again by the nature of the
business
I think the retail part of the business
is something that continues to exhibit a
relatively lower loss ratio experience
and it does tend to have a higher cost
of acquisition as we look at the ramping
up the growth opportunity again there if
you have to look at the individual loss
ratios and also kind of more or less
remained at the levels of 60 to 63
percent whether you look at fi 19 or
whether you look at effect 20 good men
women suffer at the bank at this point
hanim yeah yeah I know
continuation to the single solitary
okay thank you the next question is from
the lineup of GN doctor from fil P
squared hey hi guys thank you for taking
my question then thank you for doing
this call I had actually the questions
on market share which got addressed by
the previous caller so I'll ask the to
follow up questions one was on duration
on your fixed income book could you just
help at and how that's more to the
cocktail in that interest rates have
been volatile that was one and second
was through the year if things remain
tough if inorganic opportunities come
your way what are the areas within your
industry that you are open to to look at
just a question thank you so on the
second one we've always said that we are
open to inorganic opportunities it
should come at a price where we can
deliver value to our shareholders in
terms of giving a return and if
opportunities open up even at this time
we will always be open we would look at
what franchise incrementally we get out
of it could be a certain distribution
franchise a certain relationships or
certain businesses which could be
additive where we could something see
some synergy when if it's otherwise so
the answer to that question is yes open
but it has to get a price that it makes
sense for us in terms of the duration of
the portfolio if you see the overall
duration of our portfolio is about three
point seven two at this point in time
the duration of the portfolio last year
was over four point seven six we are
keeping it keeping the duration a bit
low because we've kept it low because we
where's having from our perspective the
long duration bonds they don't give us
an adequate margin of safety at the
levels that it it was of course one
didn't anticipate a pandemic so to that
extent it's gone down further but
pre-pandemic at those rates we were not
seeing the relative value we want to
keep our or fully o flexible so that we
could reallocate our bond portfolio in a
direction that we preferred that was our
approach
last year so we kept it slightly low so
that we could swivel wherever we wanted
to right now our our you know approaches
particularly you know given the
volatility that we've seen whenever we
are seeing some market distribution and
an interest itself going up we are
trying to lock it and slightly increase
the duration okay thank you thank you
ladies and gentlemen due to screen that
was the last great I know what about
after closing comments
oh thank you everyone thank you for
joining you know difficult things and
listen for everyone and do the Saturday
evenings though I do not know what these
days you can make out what is a Saturday
or Friday or thank you for joining stay
safe take care of yourself Thanks thanks
everyone thank you thank you thank you
ladies and gentlemen on behalf of ICICI
Lombard general insurance that concludes
this conference thank you for joining us
and you may now disconnect your lines